這是談判的條件
It's there for leverage,
成績標準就能拍板定案
so that we can lock down  performance standards.
不能把他們的勞資談判權利  當作玩牌的籌碼
You don't toss around their right to  collective bargaining like a poker chip.
不這麼做，他們不會妥協
If we don't, they won't budge.
馬帝史皮奈拉看過了嗎？
Has Marty Spinella seen this?
還沒有
Not in the version I showed him.
- 所以你當面騙他？  - 沒有
-So you lied to his face?  -No.
我修改我的承諾範圍
I revised the parameters of my promise.
- 就是說謊  - 這是政治
-Which is lying.  -Which is politics.
你最厲害的地方，鮑伯
The sort you're well-versed in, Bob.
這才是政治
Here's some politics for you.
我讓這個提案提交國會  下屆就不用選了
I allow this to go to the floor,  I get murdered next election.
這是總統的命令
This is coming from the President.
就我所知  我以前還是民主黨，法蘭
Last time I checked,  I was still a Democrat, Frank,
你也是  你是在說總統不是嗎？
and you were, too.  Are you telling me the President isn't?
因為他的表現活像共和黨
Because he's acting a hell  of a lot like a Republican.
我以為鮑伯是同一陣線
I thought Bob was on our team.
就讓他跟總統會面十分鐘
Just sit him down with the President.  Ten minutes.
我們不會談到勞資談判
We won't touch collective bargaining.
你想知道我的看法
Are you interested in my advice on this,
還是只要我傳話？
or you just want me  to deliver the message?
我一直很重視你的看法，法蘭
I'm always interested in your advice, Frank.
柏許沒錯  你會失去很多的支持
Birch is right.  You're going to burn a lot of bridges.
總統應該至少和他面談  聽聽他的想法
The President should at least sit down  with him and let him make his case.
你跟鮑伯說我很樂意  安排他和總統見面
You tell Bob I'm happy to schedule  a meeting with the President
等他定下這項提案  提交國會的日期後
once he's set a date  to put this bill on the floor.
去他的總統
The President can fuck himself.
這是他執政的政綱
This is the platform. It's what he ran on.
我不管他是什麼政綱  他不能用權力影響眾議院
I don't give a shit what he ran on.  He can't steamroll the House.
還有不要忘記  你是幫我工作，法蘭
And don't forget,  you work for me, Frank, not him.
如果他想把提案提交國會  就得直接跟我談
If he wants something on the floor,  he's gonna have to talk to me directly.
我知道你對你的男子氣概  很自豪，鮑伯
I know you take a lot of  pride in your manhood, Bob,
令人佩服
and it's impressive,
不論有多大  琳達還是能讓你吃閉門羹
but as big as it is,  Linda can still shut the door on it.
跟瓦克斯說這項提案  胎死腹中了
Tell Vasquez the bill is dead.
這不是他第一次做這樣的事
That's not the first time  he's pulled that stunt on me.
也許我不該多嘴
Probably should have held my tongue,
但我無法抗拒  看見他束手無策的機會
but I just couldn't resist the chance  to see him shrivel.
- 早安  - 法蘭
-Good morning.  -Frank.
總統先生
Mr. President.
琳達
Linda.
刪除提案裏的  反勞資談判的條款
Let's strike the anti-collective bargaining  provision from the bill.
琳達和我商量過  我覺得她的想法是對的
Linda and I have talked it over,  and I think she's right on this.
跟鮑伯說他可以明天下午過來
Tell Bob he can come by  tomorrow afternoon.
總統，恕我直言  你不應該讓他予取予求
Sir, respectfully, I do not think  you should give him the satisfaction.
- 給我一個理由  - 讓我們看起來很脆弱
-Well, give me a reason.  -Makes us appear weak.
這是你建立優勢的機會
This is an opportunity for you  to establish your supremacy.
應該把握機會
We should seize it.
如果沒有柏許的合作  我們會很辛苦
But without Birch's cooperation,  we're fighting an uphill battle
才能將提案提交國會  法蘭，我們討論過
before we even get the bill to the floor.  Frank, we discussed this.
總統，如果你現在讓步
Sir, ifyou give in now,
未來四年  柏許都會踩在你頭上
Birch will walk all over you  for the next four years.
我保證能讓提案提交眾議院
I can get this bill on the House floor as is.  I promise you.
好，法蘭  讓我瞧瞧你的本事
All right, Frank. Show me what you can do.
謝謝，總統先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
她竟想奪走我的功勞
That was her trying to take credit for my idea.
她不願意聽我的意見  太過分了
Advice she wouldn't take from me.  Unacceptable.
我不會讓她佔我便宜  拿走我的好處
I will not allow her to sell my goods  when she cuts me out of the profits.
我很明白告訴她  不准接受專訪
I specifically told her no interviews.
她不理我的命令，不只一次
She disobeyed me, not just once.
上個月至少有八次
At least eight times in the past month.
她不會走的，湯姆
She stays, Tom.
她完全不尊重我的職權  瑪格莉特
She has no respect for my authority,  Margaret.
我說她不會走
I said she stays.
這裏有規定，有做事的方式
There are rules.  There's a way of doing things.
如果記者不聽話…
If I have a reporter who won't listen...
兩個大一女生一起搬進宿舍
Two freshmen girls  are moving into their dorm room together.
一個來自喬治亞州  一個來自康乃迪克州
One of them's from Georgia,  one of them's from Connecticut.
康乃迪克州的女孩  在幫她的母親掛窗簾
Girl from Connecticut's  helping her mother put up curtains.
喬治亞州的女孩轉過身問  「你好，你們來自哪裏？」
Girl from Georgia turns to them and says,  "Hi. Where y'all from?"
康乃迪克州的女孩說  「我們
Girl from Connecticut says,  "We're from a place
「不會把前置詞放在句子最後」
"where we know not to end a  sentence with a preposition. "
喬治亞州的女孩說  「對不起
Girl from Georgia says,  "Beg my pardon.
「你們來自哪裏…
"Where y'all from...
「婊子？」
"Cunt?"
你有聽過這個嗎？
You heard that one before?
不一樣的版本  用詞沒有那麼粗俗
A version of it. With softer language.
湯姆，我們不需要  遵守規定的員工
Tom, we don't need people  who follow the rules.
我們需要有個性的員工
We need people with personality.
我們要喬伊的臉孔  還有她的活力
We want Zoe's face, her energy.
我們要她盡量上電視
We want to get her on  TV as much as possible.
可以幫我們鋪路
It helps us cut through the noise.
懂我的意思嗎？
See what I'm saying?
聽到了，瑪格莉特
I hear you, Margaret.
謝謝你，湯姆
Thank you, Tom.
謝謝你
Thank you.
進來
Come in.
我以為…
I thought...
我本來想問候艾薇琳
I wanted to say hi to Evelyn.
艾薇琳？
Evelyn?
這以前是她的辦公室
This was her office.
她沒有在這裏工作了
I don't think she works here anymore.
吉莉安柯爾  幾周前來到公司的
Gillian Cole.  I came on board a couple weeks ago.
吉莉安，世安
Gillian. WorldWell.
- 是的  - 風評很不錯，瑞米丹頓
-Yeah.  -I've heard great things. Remy Danton.
你和克萊兒一起工作？
You work with Claire?
可以這樣說
In a way.
- 你好，瑞米  - 克萊兒
-Hello, Remy.  -Claire.
- 你見過吉莉安了  - 是的，剛剛認識
-I see you've met Gillian.  -Yes, just now.
如你所見  她的工作表現很出色
She's doing fantastic work for us,  as you can see.
紅色是完成的井  綠色是可能的地點
Red is completed wells,  green, potential sites,
黃色是許可的地點  藍色是過濾中心
yellow, approved sites,  and blue are the filtration centers.
很棒，你喜歡這裏嗎？
Nice. So you liking it here?
我的屬下和我都很喜歡
Yeah. My staff and I are loving it.
克萊兒給我們很多機會
Claire's opened a lot of doors for us.
聽來像克萊兒
Sounds like Claire.
要去我的辦公室嗎？
Shall we head to my office?
- 吉莉安，很高興認識你  - 很高興認識你
-Gillian, nice to meet you.  -Nice to meet you.
怎麼回事？
What happened?
事情變複雜了
Things got complicated.
善可工業有危機
SanCorp was in a difficult situation.
我以為有危機時  你會挺身而出
I would have thought you'd step up  when things were difficult,
不會影響捐款
not hold the donation hostage.
現在情況比較緩和  捐款數目有增加
Well, things are less complicated now.  The donation is back on the table.
我必須開除公司一半的人
I had to fire half my staff.
你能請他們回來
Now you can hire them back.
善可工業準備好加倍頭筆資助
SanCorp is prepared  to double its initial commitment.
本季總額150萬
$1.5 million, lump sum, this quarter.
- 為什麼？  - 公共關係，按照往例
-Why?  -Public relations. Same as before.
他們想要法蘭斯什麼？
And what do they want from Francis?
法蘭那邊搞定了  現在只談淨水創權
Things are square with Frank.  We're only talking about the CWl.
但為何加倍？
But why double it?
因為我說應該加倍
Because I said they should.
他們給的越多，你能做得更多  他們就越有面子
The more they give, the more you can do.  The more you can do, the better they look.
所以他們僱用葛蘭頓希爾  讓他們有面子
And that's why they hired Glendon Hill,  to make them look good.
他們也僱用你  在國會裏穿針引線
And they also hired you  to get traction in Congress.
這次不一樣
Not in this case.
我們要長期合作關係，克萊兒
We want a long-term partnership, Claire.
這是未來的投資
This is an investment in the future.
我們沒有要攀關係
We're not attaching strings.
我會考慮一下
I'll think about it.
他們想盡快決定
They'd really love to move quickly on this.
我說了我會考慮
I said I'll think about it.
麥德琳，你要寄電子郵件給我  我需要書面資料
Madeleine, you have to email me this shit.  I need it in writing.
一小時前才通知
And with more than an hour's notice.
我知道，但是你要明白  我們有一個計劃
Yeah, I know that, but you have to  understand we have a plan.
我們有做事的方式，當你…
We have a way that we do this,  and when you...
好的
Okay.
算了
Fine.
好，再見
Yeah. Yeah. Bye.
麥德琳心血來潮  決定到奧蘭多一趟
Madeleine has decided to have  a spur-of-the-moment trip to Orlando
跟交友網站認識的人去
with her latest eHarmony catch.
- 沒有任何警告  - 孩子們怎麼辦？
-No heads-up, no warning.  -The kids?
他們兩點半放學
They get out of school at 2:30.
我能參加造船工業會的會議
I can do the Shipbuilder's meeting.
- 你確定嗎？  - 是啊，只是他們的公關組
-You sure?  -Yeah, it's just their public affairs team.
我能向你報告  然後明天你再連絡他們
I'll brief you,  and then you can call them tomorrow.
去接你的孩子
Go get your kids.
你好
Hey.
瑞米今早有過來辦公室
Remy came by this morning. To the office.
- 他要做什麼？  - 捐款死灰復燃
-What does he want?  -The donation's back on the table.
他們加倍到150萬
They've doubled it to $1.5 million.
- 你拒絕了，對嗎？  - 我沒有
-You said no, right?  -I didn't.
他什麼都不要，法蘭斯
He doesn't want anything from you, Francis.
拜託你，克萊兒  別那麼天真了
Come on, Claire. You know better than that.
我問過了
I specifically asked.
也許不是現在  但是我創造了這個人
Maybe not right now,  but look, I invented this guy, all right?
- 他很狡猾  - 想想這筆錢的用途
-It's a slippery slope.  -Think ofwhat I can do with this money.
我能把解雇的員工請回來
I can hire back the people I let go.
也能增加吉莉安計劃的資金
I can help accelerate the funding  for the projects that Gillian has brought in.
我們找別的方式募款
Let's find another way to raise the money.
但是這筆錢就在面前
But it's right there at my feet.
克萊兒，我現在分身乏術
Claire, I have too much  on my plate right now.
我不能讓善可工業  再緊盯著我不放
I can't have SanCorp  breathing down my neck again.
我不能讓瑞米…
I can't have Remy...
就是瑞米
Look, it is Remy.
他太瞭解我了，這樣很危險
He knows me too well. It's dangerous.
要看全局
Look at the bigger picture here.
我求你
I'm asking.
你才不是
No. You're not.
克萊兒
Claire.
我告訴你我給他的回答
I'll tell you what I told him.
- 是什麼？  - 我會考慮
-Which was?  -I'll think about it.
我知道我們有些不愉快  也許是我的關係
I know there's been some tension,  and I'm probably more to blame than you are.
但我想忘掉這件事
But I'd like to put that behind us.
喬伊，你將成為  我們的新白宮記者
Zoe, you're going to be our new  White House correspondent.
珍妮呢？
What about Janine?
我把她升到中西部分社主任
I promoted her to Midwest Bureau Chief.
她同意嗎？她想放棄白宮？
She's okay with that?  She wants to give up the White House?
這是我做的決定
It's the decision I've made.
我只是覺得珍妮經驗很豐富
It's just that Janine has so much experience.
我以為你會很興奮
I thought you'd be more excited about this.
對不起，我以為  你叫我過來這裏是要…
I'm sorry. I just thought  you brought me in here to... I don't know.
- 炒你魷魚  - 也許
-To fire you.  -Maybe.
過去的事別提了
Water under the bridge.
我們重新開始
We're starting over.
你準備好了嗎？
So are you ready to take this on?
我能考慮嗎？
Can I think about it?
有機會去白宮  通常沒有人要考慮，喬伊
People usually don't have to think about it  when they're offered the White House, Zoe.
一兩天就好
Just a day or two.
珍妮訂了週五的機票  飛去芝加哥
Janine is booked for a flight to Chicago  on Friday.
我會在那之前跟你說  我只是需要…
I'll let you know before then. I just need to...
謝謝你，湯姆
Thank you. Thank you, Tom.
大衛拉斯穆森是多數黨領袖  表示他比我高一級
David Rasmussen is the majority leader,  which means he's one step above me
比柏許低一級  他是飢不擇食的貪官
and one below Birch, which is akin to being  between a very hungry wolf
可是喜愛爭吵的雙面人
and a very quarrelsome sheep.
讓我們看他是要往哪邊倒
Let's see if he stays with the herd  or joins the pack.
大衛，可以和你一起吃嗎？
David. You mind if I join you?
當然，只吃沙拉？
Please. A salad, huh?
我想多照顧自己的身體
Yes. I'm trying to take better care of myself.
好男人，節食嗎？
Good man. Diet?
節食、運動，什麼都來
Diet, exercise, everything.
你也該好好照顧自己
You ought to take better care  of yourself, too.
那麼他們應該不要  再供應這麼美味的披薩
Well, then they should stop  serving such good pizza.
我不是在說吃的
I'm not talking about the food.
我是在說柏許
I'm talking about Birch.
你不處理他的話  絕對不會當上發言人
You are never going to be Speaker  unless you do something about it.
我很滿意我現在的位置
I'm very satisfied where I am.
- 拜託  - 目前來說
-Come on.  -For the time being, yeah.
目前表示永遠
Time being never.
如果柏許敗選或退休  你才能當上發言人
The only way you become Speaker  is if Birch loses his district or retires,
這兩種情況  都不可能太快發生
neither ofwhich is going to happen  before you and I have dentures.
我不太喜歡談這個，法蘭
I'm not happy where this  conversation is going, Frank.
如果你要，我知道你想要  有一個方式
If you want it, and I know you do,  there's a way.
好，我不能…
Okay. Right. I can't...
你只需要簡單多數  218張選票
All you need is a simple majority. 218 votes.
共和黨那邊  我們至少有205張選票
We're going to get at least 205  out of the GOP,
你只要13張民主黨的選票
and after that, all you need is 13 Democrats.
你跟我就兩張票了
You and I make two.
你瘋啦？
Are you out of your mind?
稍微想一下
Just consider it for a moment.
你要跟共和黨串通？
You want to collude with the Republicans?
我不想，但是如果能讓你  當上發言人，我會
I don't want to, but I would  if you become Speaker in the process.
沒做過這種事
Never been done before.
凡事都有第一次
There's a first time for everything.
太荒謬了
This is ridiculous.
共和黨應該會很想有機會  壓壓鮑伯的氣焰
The Republicans would love a chance  to knock Bob down a peg or two.
你想幫他們？
And you want to help them?
我想幫我們
I want to help us.
鮑伯不會跟白宮妥協
Bob will not play ball with the White House.
大衛，你比較講道理  但他不是
Now, you're a reasonable man, David,  and he's not.
你知道我是什麼樣的人？
You know what I am?
我是個很小心的人
I'm a discreet man.
你很幸運
You're lucky for that.
我不會跟鮑伯提這件事  但是如果你再提
I'm not going to mention this to Bob,  but if you ever bring it up again,
我就沒有辦法了
I won't have a choice.
看來他選了軟弱那邊
Looks like he opted for the herd.
克萊兒，我想訂一些濾水器
Claire. I'd like to put an  order for the water filters
還有鑿井的機器  南蘇丹計劃要用的
and the well-digging equipment  for the South Sudan project.
能討論一下預算嗎？
Can we talk about the budget?
- 多少？  - 20萬
-How much?  -$200,000.
給一個計劃？
For one project?
我知道數目龐大  但這會是非洲的旗艦計劃
I know it's a lot, but it'll be  our flagship project in Africa,
我們會是第一家  在那裏有這種規模的公司
and we would be the first organization there  to work on this scale.
- 我想先明白細節  - 預算在我這裏
-I'd like to go over the specifics first.  -I have the budget right here.
我先看看有沒有留言  再過去你那邊
Let me just grab my messages,  and then I'll come in to you.
好的，我會在我辦公室
Okay. I'll be in my office.
我不在的時候  有人打電話來嗎？
Any calls while I was out?
留言在桌子上  郵差送來這個包裹
They're on the desk,  and this came by messenger.
克萊兒，你不需要善可工業  你有我！
亞當，我是克萊兒
Adam. It's Claire.
我知道
Yes. I know. It has.
沒事，只是突然想起你
No reason. I was just thinking about you.
你沒錯，我說謊了，我有事
You're right. It is a lie. I do have a reason.
我需要利用你
I need to use you.
白宮是新聞的墓地  所有的事都是假造的
The White House is where news goes to die.  Everything's canned.
- 這些完美的聲明…  - 這是很有聲望的工作，喬伊
-These perfectly prepared statements...  -It's a prestigious job, Zoe.
以前在我高中的時候是  現在是墓地
Used to be, when I was in ninth grade.  Now it's a graveyard.
唯一稍微有趣的事  是每年一次的晚宴
The only halfway interesting thing they do  is throw a big dinner party once a year
他們會跟電影明星打交道  自我安慰
where they pat themselves on the back  and rub shoulders with movie stars.
- 誰會想去啊  - 從你來報社開始
-Who needs that?  -Every day since you started here,
你就一直求我升你職  但是你現在…
you've begged me to move you up,  and now suddenly...
我的人生目標  不是在《先軀報》往上爬
My goal in life is not  to climb up The Herald's ladder
直到我有自己的文具
one rung at a time until  I've got my own stationery.
有些人很珍惜這種報社的職業
Some of us value a career at a paper like this.
對不起，我不是故意要這樣說…
I'm sorry. I didn't mean for that to come off...
算了，還有你少爬了幾步
Well, it did, and you skipped a few rungs,  by the way.
你想怎樣就怎樣，喬伊  但如果你希望我會鼓勵你
Do what you want to do, Zoe,  but if you want me to be your cheerleader
「沒關係，拒絕吧」，我不會
and say, "Yeah, turn it down," I won't.
我剛來報社時  會不顧一切爭取那份工作
I would have killed for that job  when I first started here.
把菲許那放到  「偏向贊成票」那欄
Put Fichner in the "leaning yes" column.
- 你不覺得他是中立嗎？  - 他恨柏許
-Don't you think he's a neutral?  -He hates Birch.
但是他欠柏許人情
Yeah, but he owes Birch  for the Ways and Means appointment.
放他在「中立」，還有誰？
Put him in "neutral." Who else?
拉米茲也是中立嗎？
Ramirez as a neutral?
這個名單真不可靠
This list is so shaky.
只要有一人洩露給鮑伯…  我們需要一個名字
Any one of them leaks it to Bob...  No, what we need is one name.
一個人可以拿12張選票
One person who can deliver 1 2.
黑人核心小組
The Black Caucus.
沃麥克
Womack.
- 我們可以給他什麼？  - 他需要什麼？
-What can we offer him?  -What does he need?
我來看看他的檔案
Let me pull up his file.
在這裏
Here we go.
麥卡汀空軍基地  在他的選區有三千名員工
McCuddin Airforce base  employs 3,000 people in his district.
是國防部今年要去除的一塊
It's on the DOD's chopping block this year.
基地重組與關閉委員會  有人脈嗎？
Who do we know on the BRAC commission?
那太危險了
That's dangerous.
這條路會讓人知道  我們設法影響這兩個單位
The trail leads back to us  trying to influence the DOD or the BRAC.
不是  我們要關閉另外一個基地
No, no, no.  What we do is we close another base.
國防部預算留下足夠的經費
We leave enough money in the DOD's budget
讓沃麥克的基地不被影響
to keep Womack's base off the list.
我們需要…
What we need...
一個自己人
Is someone we own.
彼得魯索
爸爸，我餓了
Dad, I'm hungry.
來了，孩子
Coming, buddy.
拿去
Here we go.
有起司，沒有起司
With cheese. Without cheese.
爸爸？
Dad?
幹嘛？
Yeah.
那個看起來很噁心
That looks pretty disgusting.
沒錯，看起來很噁心
Yeah, it looks disgusting.
外表不重要，好吃就好了
It's not how it looks, it's how it tastes.
拿個叉子
And a fork would be nice.
好的，等一下
Shit. Okay. Hold on.
- 你好  - 晚安，魯索先生
-Hello.  -Good evening, Mr. Russo.
安德沃先生來找你
There's a Mr. Underwood here to see you.
好的，讓他上來
Okay. Send him up.
你們好
Hi, there.
- 你好  - 你好
-Hi.  -Hi.
這是凱文，這是莎拉
This is Kevin, this is Sarah.
我是法蘭  很高興認識你們兩位
Hi. I'm Frank. Nice to meet you both.
- 你和我爸一起工作嗎？  - 是的
-Do you work with Dad?  -I do.
安德沃議員是爸爸的上司
Congressman Underwood is Daddy's boss.
我以為你沒有上司
I thought you didn't have a boss.
每個人都有上司，甜心  連議員也有
Everybody has a boss, sweetheart,  even Congressmen.
你們把晚餐拿進房間吃好了
Why don't you take your  dinner and go into the bedroom?
- 可是我想看電視  - 進去了
-But I wanted to watch TV.  -Go now.
孩子很可愛
Cute kids.
是啊，我喜歡他們  要喝點什麼嗎？
Yeah, I like them. Can I get you a drink?
不用了，我坐坐就走
No, I won't be here long.
請坐
Yeah. Have a seat.
謝謝你，這是掌上型電動嗎？
Thank you. Is that a PS Vita?
他有哪些遊戲？
Which games does he have?
- 統統都有  - 我家有一個主機型的
-All of them.  -I have a console at home.
我有時會玩玩紓解壓力  應該在車裏也裝一台
I play sometimes to relax.  I ought to get one of these for the car.
彼得，我們必須關閉  你選區裏的造船廠
So, Peter, we need to close  the shipyard in your district.
明天基地重組與關閉聽證會  你不要像平常一樣爭辯
The BRAC hearing is tomorrow.  You won't put up your usual fight.
也不要加任何證詞
You have zero testimony to add.
- 我不能這樣做  - 你可以的，彼得
-I can't do that.  -Yes, you can, Peter.
我花了數月準備證詞  遊說委員會和整個辦公室…
I spent months on that testimony.  I lobbied the commission. My entire office...
我相信你費盡精神  但可惜，無法開花結果
I'm sure you've done splendid work,  but unfortunately, it can't come to fruition.
- 為什麼？  - 政治
-Why?  -Politics.
有比我們更有能力的人  在影響大局
There's forces bigger than  either of us at play here.
有一萬兩千個工作
It's 12,000 jobs.
我知道，很可惜
I know. It's a shame.
我承諾讓造船廠繼續運作  才能當選
Keeping that shipyard open  is what got me elected.
那些人是我的朋友
Those people are my friends.
我不是來跟你爭辯的，彼得
I'm not here to debate this, Peter.
基地會關閉
The base will close.
唯一的問題是  你要不要快刀斬亂麻？
The only question is, will you make it  a swift death or a painful one?
不行，我不能這麼做
No way. I won't sit on my hands.
我明白這對你來說很困難
I sympathize that this is  gonna be difficult for you.
我不知道該怎麼補償你  但是我會的，彼得
And I don't know how yet,  but I will make it up to you, Peter.
我是一個有權有勢的朋友
I'm a powerful friend to have right now,
也許是你唯一的朋友
perhaps your only friend,
所以不要反抗我
so don't defy me.
對家庭的愛
Love of family.
大多數政客永遠拿這句話  家庭價值當作口號
Most politicians are permanently chained  to that slogan. Family values.
但是當我發現你找妓女的時候
But when you cozy up to hookers  and I find out,
我會要你為你的虛偽付出代價
I will make that hypocrisy hurt.
有收到我送你的禮物嗎？
Did you get the present I sent you?
那不算禮物
You wouldn't really call it a present.
好吧，一個溫和的提醒
Well, more of a gentle reminder, maybe.
應該說是笨手笨腳  讓我很驚訝
More heavy-handed than gentle,  which surprised me.
不像你的作風，法蘭斯
It's not really your style, Francis.
不過我收到了
But, yes. I got it.
我喜歡那件
I like that one.
- 我也是  - 但是第一件比較好
-I do, too.  -But the first one's better.
你覺得嗎？
You think?
明天有特別的事嗎？
Something special tomorrow?
亞當蓋羅威要從紐約來
Adam Galloway's  coming down from New York.
來做什麼？
What for?
因為下個月的無聲拍賣慈善會  需要他的一些照片
Because I need some of his photographs  for the silent auction at the gala next month.
和瑞米說了嗎？
You speak to Remy yet?
還沒有
I haven't.
如果你想看起來比較迷人  穿黑色那件
If you want to look inviting,  wear the black one.
你好
Hello.
好的，很好，謝謝
Okay. Great. Thanks.
亞當？
Adam?
你是用什麼方法保持的？
How is it the world keeps spinning  and you manage to stay ahead of it?
- 大衛同意了嗎？  - 是他的想法
-David's on board with this?  -lt was his idea.
為什麼他不在？
Then why isn't he here?
我們在完成以前要很小心
Well, we have to be careful  until it's a done deal.
- 我不確定，法蘭  - 想一想吧，泰利
-I don't know, Frank.  -Think about it, Terry.
你可能成為美國國會首位
You could become the first  African-American majority leader
黑人多數黨領袖
in the United States Congress.
我們一起創造歷史
Let's make some history.
你不在乎歷史
You don't care about history.
你找我只是因為  我能幫你拿到足夠的選票
You just wanted me because  I can round up the votes.
我需要選票，也在乎歷史
I need the votes, and I do care about history,
但最重要的是，泰利  你知道怎麼當多數黨領袖
but most importantly, Terry,  you know how to lead.
你是黑人核心小組召集人  是有原因的
You're the head of the  Black Caucus for a reason.
大衛成為發言人  我成為多數黨領袖…
So David becomes speaker,  I become majority leader...
我繼續當黨鞭
And I stay on as Whip.
為什麼你自己  不想當多數黨領袖？
Why don't you want majority  leader for yourself?
我對現在的情況很滿意
I'm satisfied where I am.
也許有一天當你成為發言人  你會升我的官
Maybe one day, when you become Speaker,  you'll bump me up.
這種事情是無法回頭的
This is the sort of thing  that there's no turning back.
我能錦上添花
I can throw a cherry on top.
麥卡汀基地不會關閉
McCuddin stays open.
怎麼會？
How?
你不會想知道
You don't want to know how.
你只要保留選區三千個工作  就會上頭條
You just want the headline  when you keep 3,000 jobs in your district.
- 12票？  - 12票
-12 votes?  -12 votes.
我可以給你10到11票
I can get you 10, probably 11.
跟一個識貨的人合作真爽快
It's so refreshing to work with someone  who will throw a saddle on a gift horse
比不懂的人好太多了
rather than look it in the mouth.
不錯
That's nice.
我在安拉瓦提市郊的村子  找到她的
I found her in a village outside Amravati.
她叫泰伊拉
Her name was Tyala.
我拍下那張照片三周後  她就過世了
She died three weeks after I took that picture.
真可憐
That's awful.
你如果喜歡能全拿走
You can have them all if you like.
我喜歡你剪短髮
I love your hair short.
今晚有事嗎？
You have plans tonight?
沒有
No.
法蘭會在家嗎？
Is Frank expecting you home?
我相信他會很晚回家
I'm sure he'll be home late.
一起吃晚飯
Get dinner with me.
你搭幾點的火車？
What time is your train?
我只買單程票
I don't book round-trip tickets.
我沒有那麼快下班
It's going to be a while before I can leave.
你幾點會做完？
What time will you be done?
大概8點左右
Probably around 8:00.
我會選個地方，再跟你說
I'll pick a place, let you know.
大衛
David.
你好嗎，喬？
How are you, Joe?
我支持你，就這麼做吧
I'm behind you. Let's do this.
做什麼？
Do what?
不給人看你的底牌，我喜歡
Keep your cards close. I like that.
你好，這是1214號房
Hi. Yeah. This is room 1 214.
我想點一瓶溫巴赫
I'd like a bottle of the Weinbach, please.
對，兩瓶好了
Yeah.  Actually, could you make that two bottles?
謝謝你
Thank you.
坐吧，你讓我很緊張
Sit down. You're making me nervous.
- 你還在抽煙？  - 偶爾
-You still smoke?  -From time to time, yes.
我戒了，這是假象
I quit. These are an illusion.
- 你要嗎？  - 好的
-You want?  -Sure.
怎麼了？
What?
現在不行
Not now.
好吧
Okay.
我該走了
I should go.
- 我以為…  - 我知道
-I just...assumed...  -I know.
我們不能再這樣
We can't start this again.
當我結束一件事  就是徹底了結
When I end something, I end it.
你為什麼要我大老遠  從紐約過來？
So why'd you have me come all  the way down from New York?
這是一個錯誤
It was a mistake.
對不起，亞當  我應該公事公辦的
I'm sorry, Adam. I should've kept it business.
我最不喜歡你那一面
Side of you I like the least.
沒有錯誤，克萊兒
There are no mistakes, Claire.
- 你好  - 你好
-Hi.  -Hello.
再來一點酒？
More wine?
你今天好嗎？
How was your day?
- 很好  - 亞當呢？
-Good.  -Adam well?
他也很好
He is.
我們剛剛一起吃飯
We just had dinner.
我在回家的路上  寫了電子郵件給瑞米
I emailed Remy on the way home.
我跟他說我不要錢
I told him I'm not taking the money.
謝謝，我知道這很不容易
Thank you.  I appreciate that this was not easy.
我們不喜歡容易的事，對嗎？
Well, we don't like easy, do we?
所有的證據都如此
All the evidence would suggest it.
霍本夫婦週三  可以來家裏吃晚飯嗎？
Is it all right if the Holburns  come over for dinner Wednesday night?
我想請費莉絲  為慈善會買些桌子
I want Felicity to buy  some tables for the gala.
當然好啊
Yeah, of course.
我需要議員跟參議員來
I'm going to need  Congressmen and senators there.
- 你要動用人脈  - 沒問題
-You need to call in favors.  -Done.
要很多人
Not a few, a lot.
我明早會開始連絡
I'll start making calls in the morning.
亞當捐了十幅照片
Adam donated 10 photographs.
他很大方
That was generous of him.
他住在東方酒店
He's staying at the Mandarin.
你呢？
And you?
這裏
Here.
但試驗場的重要性
But the Proving Ground's importance
比策略地理價值要高
stems far beyond its  strategic geographic value.
亞伯丁試驗場的軍事物質研發
APG's research and  development of military materiel
是我國反恐努力的中心
is central to our nation's  counter-terrorism efforts.
基地裏有預防性藥物的  研究實驗室
The base houses research laboratories  for preventative medicine
也有軍職人員的各種訓練場
as well as a wide variety of training grounds  for military personnel.
亞伯丁試驗場  也創造了很多工作
APG is also a job creator.
一年提供四億的薪資
It provides $400 million in payroll annually,
還有將近五億的合約
and nearly $500 million in contracts.
謝謝你今天  給我這個作證的機會
Thank you for the opportunity  to testify before you today.
馬裏蘭議員有任何問題嗎？
Any questions for the  Congresswoman from Maryland?
沒有
No.
贊成亞伯丁試驗場
Those in favor of removing  the Aberdeen Proving Ground
不須關閉的人？
from the list of closures?
- 贊成  - 贊成
-Aye.  -Aye.
記錄下來通過
So noted and removed.
接下來我們要討論  費城海軍造船廠
Okay, we'll next consider  the Philadelphia Naval Shipyard.
賓州第一選區議員
Would the congressman from  Pennsylvania's first district
請出席作證
Iike to offer testimony?
主席  愛德華勞羅斯
我沒有證詞
I have no testimony to offer.
但是我們會創造不同的…
Yeah, but the difference  that we're gonna make...
泰利，我待會再回電
Terry, let me call you right back.
泰利沃麥克？
Terry Womack?
沒錯
Possibly.
三位黑人核心小組的成員  告訴我
I've had three members of  the Black Caucus tell me
要支持我當發言人
they're backing my play for the speakership.
- 很有趣  - 我覺得
-lnteresting.  -I have a sense
你在散播一些不實謠言
you've been disseminating  some misinformation.
恐怕是你聽到不實消息，大衛
No. I'm afraid it's you  who are misinformed, David.
不只有三位成員支持你  而是十位
You don't have three members backing you.  You have 10.
我跟你說得很清楚  我不願意蹚這個渾水
I made it very clear I didn't want  any part of this.
你說得很清楚
Yes, you made it crystal clear.
那你為什麼亂說話？
Then why are you telling people?
因為他們不知道你說得很清楚
Because they don't know  you made it crystal clear.
我必須跟鮑伯說
I have to go to Bob with this.
他會認為你安排一場政變
He'll think you organized a coup,
打了退堂鼓，然後讓我頂罪
got cold feet,  and are making me the scapegoat.
大衛，如果我現在拿起電話
David, if I pick up this phone right now
把消息傳出去
and leak this story,
鮑伯只能讓你走人
Bob will have no choice but to drop you,
就算他會相信你的說法
even if he believes your version of events.
你要坐嗎？
You wanna take a seat?
弗萊迪烤肉舖
- 弗萊迪？  - 什麼事，法蘭？
-Freddy?  -Yeah, Frank?
你做一半就好  我今晚吃了很多
You better make it a half order.  I got a big dinner tonight.
沒問題
Sure thing.
- 甘藍沙拉？好的  - 照舊
-Slaw? You got it.  -Always.
拿去吧
Here you go.
有什麼新聞嗎？
So, what's the latest?
沒什麼，還是老樣子
You know, Frank. Same old shit.
上週末差點沒命
Almost got killed last weekend.
- 這裏？  - 不是
-Here?  -No.
維吉尼亞州的州展
State fair down in Virginia.
我跟我哥搬這個烤箱過去
Me and my brother hauling  this smoker down there,
一輛該死的小卡車  把一台冰箱綁在車頂
and this fucking minivan  had a fridge strapped on top.
把一台冰箱  綁在小卡車的車頂，法蘭
A fridge strapped on top of a minivan, Frank.
- 太愚蠢了  - 結果冰箱松滑
-That's stupid.  -Well, that fridge slipped loose.
就掉在我們面前  我緊急左轉，差點就撞到了
Right in front of us.  I had to swerve to the left. Barely missed it.
然後我們的烤箱開始晃動  差點砸到旁邊的掀背車
But now that smoker is fishtailing,  almost hit a hatchback in the next lane.
緊急右轉，也差點撞到
Swerved to the right.  Barely missed that, too.
- 老天  - 是真的
-Jesus.  -Man, it was real.
這就是上帝  賜給我們本能反應的原因
But, you know, that's  why God gave us reflexes.
才能緊急躲開  突然砸下來的冰箱
So we can move the fuck out of the way  when a fridge come out of nowhere.
- 肋排如何？  - 你知道的
-How are them ribs?  -You know how they are.
- 你知道我愛聽  - 完美，弗萊迪
-You know I like to hear it.  -Perfection, Freddy.
完美
Perfection.
- 好好享用，法蘭  - 謝謝，弗萊迪
-You go on ahead, Frank.  -Thank you, Freddy.
真是出乎意料
Well, this is a surprise.
- 你通常會傳簡訊  - 你在哪裏？
-You usually text.  -Where are you?
在貧民區  試著找尋生命的意義
On the other side of the tracks  trying to find the meaning of life.
有找到我要的嗎？
Find anything for me?
你是說有新聞價值的事？
You mean anything newsworthy?
我不是打來煩你的
I actually didn't call to badger you.
你的確有  但是還蠻討人喜歡的
Yes, you did, but that's part ofyour charm.
我是要告訴你
No. I wanted to tell you that
我升職擔任白宮記者
I've been promoted  to White House correspondent.
我會跟媒體記者團一起行動  參加簡報
I'll have to travel with the press corps,  be at briefings,
但是我可以想辦法
but I can work around all that.
如果你需要我的話  不會有任何改變
If you need me. It won't change anything.
剛好相反，這改變一切
On the contrary. This changes everything.
不會，我可以適應
No. I can be flexible.
我不需要會適應的人  我要有時間的人
I'm not interested in someone who's flexible,  I'm interested in someone who's available.
我應該拒絕嗎？
So you think I should turn it down?
那是你的決定
That's entirely up to you.
還沒正式宣佈
Well, I mean, it's not official yet.
- 我能…  - 我要走了
-I could...  -Look, I've got to go,
但如果你有時間，再打給我
but call me, you know, if you  find yourself available again.
弗萊迪相信  如果冰箱從小卡車滑下來
You see, Freddy believes that  if a fridge falls off a minivan,
你最好閃開
you better swerve out of its way.
我相信是冰箱要閃我
I believe it's the fridge's  job to swerve out of mine.
你好，珍妮…
Hey, Janine...
繼續往前走，喬伊  我現在不想跟你說話
Keep walking, Zoe.  I really don't want to talk to you right now.
我沒有要求他  他直接把我叫進辦公室…
It's not like I asked him for it.  He just called me into his office, and...
拜託，你一直覬覦我的工作
Please. You've been gunning for my job
從你第一天含著棒棒糖  來上班開始
since the day you bounced in here  with a lollipop in your mouth.
恭喜
Congratulations.
我會從中西部送你一瓶香檳
I'll send you a bottle of champagne  from the Middle West,
管他那是什麼地方
wherever the fuck that is.
我會拒絕這份工作  你不用離開
I'm gonna turn it down.  You don't have to leave.
你是想炫耀嗎？
Are you trying to rub this in or something?
請相信我，你才應該在白宮
Please believe me.  You should be in the White House.
我不想要，我從來都不想要
I don't want it. I never did.
希望我們可以一起去找湯姆
I was hoping we could go see Tom together.
- 我要他知道我們都…  - 快走開
-I want him to know that we both...  -Get the fuck out of my face.
我真心請求你  我不想要這份工作
I'm asking. For real. I don't want the job.
那你真的比我想的還笨
Then you're an even bigger  idiot than I thought you were.
在我發火前快走
Go. Before I get violent.
彼得？
Peter?
有人嗎？
Hello?
你好，我是克裏絲汀娜  我跟你爸爸一起工作
Hi. My name is Christina.  I work with your dad.
- 他不在  - 他去哪裏？
-He's not here.  -Where'd he go?
我不知道  他說他一會兒就回來
I don't know.  He said he'd be back in a little while.
什麼時候走的？
When was that?
在他接我們放學回家後
When he dropped us home from school.
他忘了拿手機
He left his phone here.
你是我爸的女朋友嗎？
Are you Dad's girlfriend?
不是，我跟你爸一起工作
No. No. I work for your dad.
那你為什麼有他的公寓鑰匙？
Then why do you have  the keys to his apartment?
你會做果醬餡餅嗎？
Will you make us Pop-Tarts?
真是太美味了，克萊兒
It was just sublime, Claire.
- 謝謝  - 我會撐上一周
-Thank you.  -I don't think I'll eat for a week.
那是表示不想吃甜點了？
Does that mean no room for dessert?
我很想，不過吃不下了
I'd love to, but none for me.
我跟你到樓下喝點白蘭地  抽點雪茄
Why don't you and I head downstairs  for a little brandy and some cigars?
古巴的嗎？
Cubans?
你不會以為我只有合法的吧？
You don't think I smoke  anything legal, do you?
- 甜點？  - 不了，謝謝
-Dessert for you?  -No. No, thanks.
但我可以再來一點香檳
But I will take a refill  of this Chardonnay, though.
當然，快沒有了，我再去拿
Of course. This is almost out.  I'll grab another.
我很討厭那種沒有警告  忽然就發生的感覺
I hate how they just hit you like that  with no warning.
你也會盜汗嗎？
You get night sweats, too?
最近開始的
This is very new to me.
法蘭知道嗎？
Does Frank know?
我還沒…我們還沒…不知道
I haven't... We haven't... No.
對不起，我們不用談這些
I'm sorry. We don't have to talk about this.
沒關係，我只是…
No. It's fine. I'm just...
沒關係，我好多了
It's fine. I feel better now.
- 可以再一點嗎？  - 當然
-Could I have a little bit more?  -Sure.
- 看你要多少  - 查理斯今晚要開車…
-Just say when.  -Charles is driving tonight, so...
夠了
And when.
- 乾杯  - 乾杯
-Cheers.  -Cheers.
你邀請我時  有提到淨水創權的事
So, you mentioned,  when you invited me, the CWl.
你要辦慈善會發表新的…
You're having a gala  and launching some new...
沒錯
Yes, that's right.
有個精明能幹的年輕女性
We just brought on this  brilliant young woman
會幫我們拓展海外計劃
who's going to help us  expand our efforts overseas.
克萊兒，我就直說了
Claire, I will save you the trouble.
查理斯和我很希望能幫忙
Charles and I would be  delighted to contribute.
費莉絲，你真大方
Well, that's very generous ofyou, Felicity.
你也很貼心  給我們傑弗遜晚宴的入場券
Well, you were such a darling,  getting us tickets to the Jefferson Ball.
- 那沒什麼  - 才不是的
-That was nothing.  -lt wasn't nothing.
那是…
It was...
這個城市的人  不會無緣無故對人家好
People in this town don't go out of their way  to be nice to each other.
查理斯和我在這裏14年了…
Fourteen years Charles and l  have been here, and...
不論怎麼說
Anyway,
我很高興有個朋友
I'm grateful to have a friend.
你需要多少？
How much do you need?
克裏絲汀娜  你在這裏做什麼？
Christina, what the fuck are you doing here?
他們睡了
They're sleeping.
彼得
Peter.
- 爸爸  - 孩子
-Hey, Dad.  -Hey, kiddo.
你可以帶弟弟上樓嗎？
Would you take your brother downstairs?
- 我馬上來  - 拜拜，爸爸
-I'll be there in a second.  -Okay. Bye, Dad.
- 拜  - 拜？他們要去哪裏？
-Bye.  -Bye? Where they going?
我要帶他們到奶奶家
I'm taking them to their grandmother's.
我找到麥德琳，告訴她…
I was able to get ahold of  Madeleine, and I told her...
你沒有跟她說吧？
Fuck. You didn't tell her?
沒有，不過我應該要說的
No, I didn't. But I should have.
我跟她說你要出公差
I told her that you had to travel for work,
這是我最後一次幫你說謊
which is the last time I ever lie for you.
聽著…
Look...
怎麼回事，彼得？
What happened, Peter?
基地重組與關閉聽證會的事  我很抱歉
I'm sorry about the BRAC hearing.
別管那件事  你的小孩怎麼辦？
Fuck the BRAC hearing.  What about your kids?
我送他們過去就不管了
After I drop them off, I'm done.
我不再是你的女朋友  也不再為你工作
I am no longer your girlfriend.  I no longer work for you.
克裏絲汀娜…
No. Hey, Christina...
我不要聽，彼得  這次沒有藉口
I don't want to hear it, Peter.  There's no excuse this time.
- 我沒有多少時間，法蘭  - 我會簡短地說
-I don't have much time, Frank.  -I'll make it short.
- 是總統嗎？  - 不是，發言人的職務
-The President?  -No. The speakership.
大衛想當
David's making a play.
- 什麼？  - 他來找我支持
-What?  -He came to me for support.
我本來想跟你說的
My first thought was to tell you right away,
但是後來我想那樣不妥
but then my second thought  was to ignore my first thought,
因為我們有選票，鮑伯
because we have the votes, Bob.
如果有黨員反叛，我會知道的
If there had been a party revolt,  I would've known about it.
我們不需要整個黨都反叛  只要13位…
We don't need the whole party to revolt.  We need 13...
13位自由黨員  加上我們這邊的人
Thirteen Democrats,  plus the other side of the aisle.
你瘋了嗎？
Are you out of your mind?
最近大家都問我那個問題  我覺得有可能
People have been asking me that a lot lately.  I'm inclined to start saying yes.
是哪13個人？
Who are they, the 13?
大衛和我就兩張票了  泰利沃麥克
David and I are two, Terry Womack,
還有黑人核心小組10位成員  剛好11個人
and 10 members of the Black Caucus  make another 11.
總統也支持嗎？
Is the President behind this?
他不知道
No. He doesn't have a clue.
這是大衛的計劃由我來執行
This was David's plan executed by me.
但對你有好處，鮑伯
But there is an out for you, Bob.
我可以控制沃麥克
I can sway Womack either way
只要你讓他當上  下屆多數黨領袖
as long as you make him  the next majority leader.
還有…
And...
- 教育提案  - 現在我們有共識了
-The Education Bill.  -Now we're on the same page.
你知道我不能這樣做
I can't do that. You know I can't.
你是發言人，鮑伯  你能隻手遮天
You're the Speaker, Bob.  You can do anything you'd like.
老實說，指派首位  黑人多數黨領袖
And I have to say, appointing the first  African-American majority leader,
是個不錯的成就
why, that isn't a bad legacy to have.
對不起，我改變主意了
I'm sorry. I changed my mind.
我有考慮過…
I thought about it, and...
我給了你兩天考慮
Thinking about it was what  those two days were for.
我有多考慮了一些  我發現我…
And then I thought about it  some more, and I realized l...
天啊，你真的不可理喻
Jesus Christ, you're fucking unbelievable.
湯姆，我很感謝你  給我機會，但…
Look, Tom, I appreciate the fact  that you took a chance on me, but...
我不覺得你有任何感謝
No, I don't think you do.  I don't think you appreciate anything.
你是一個不懂感恩  自視甚高的小…
I think you're an ungrateful,  self-entitled little...
小什麼？
Little what?
小什麼，湯姆？說啊
Little what, Tom? Say it.
婊子，你是個婊子
Cunt. You're a cunt.
你在做什麼？
What are you doing?
你不要太過分…
Don't you dare...
你根本不知道我在打什麼
You don't even know what I'm typing.
- 滾出去，喬伊  - 再一會兒，馬上就好
-Get out, Zoe.  -Just a second. I'm almost done.
滾出去，你被開除了
Get out. You're fired.
不過你想如何自我安慰，湯姆
Whatever you have to tell yourself, Tom.
滾出去！
Get out!
我該不該送出去？
So should I press send?
我覺得應該要
I think I should.
隨你叫我什麼都好
Call me whatever you want,
但是你應該要記得，這個時代
but you should remember, these days,
當你跟一個人說話  就是跟一千個人說
when you're talking to one person,  you're talking to a 1,000.
《華府先驅報》
你會說你要多花一點時間
Well, you'll say you  wanted to spend more time
專注在你的選區
focusing on your home district.
你會說沃麥克  是很適合的接棒人選
You'll say Womack is the  right man to fill your shoes.
你不會製造新聞  也不會接受採訪
You won't make waves.  You won't do interviews.
你會默默接受當一個合群者
You'll suck it up and be a team player.
這是法蘭的點子
This was Frank's idea.
我就說他會嫁禍我
I told you he was gonna  try to blame me on it.
去找沃麥克談
Ask around. Talk to Womack.
談過了，他說你去找他的
I did. He said you came to him.
他在說謊，鮑伯！我從來…
He's fucking lying, Bob! I would never...
閉嘴，大衛
Shut up, David.
你明白我們宣佈時  你該怎麼做嗎？
Do you understand how you're to behave  when we make the announcement?
要是我不配合呢？
And if I don't play along?
那民主黨國會競選委員會  就會把所有資源
Then the DCCC will  pour everything it's got
投入你下屆選舉的競爭對手
into your primary opponent's  campaign next cycle.
我們會孤立你  然後看著你自生自滅
We'll cleave you from the herd  and watch you die in the wilderness.
告訴我們你的決定，大衛
Tell us now, David.
如果你覺得這樣最好，羅伯特
If you think it's best, Robert.
想想看  他可能是披著羊皮的狼
And just think, he could have been a wolf.
你抽出時間了
You made yourself available.
我不做了，那個爛報社
I quit. Fuck that place.
像個監牢一樣，我現在自由了
It was a prison. I'm free now.
恭喜
Congratulations.
你在哪裏？
Where are you?
- 在車上  - 我也是
-ln a car.  -So am l.
你要去哪裏？
Where you headed?
- 回家  - 我也是
-Home.  -So am l.
去你家還是我家？
To your home or mine?
你在邀請我嗎？
Is that an invitation?
隨便你想
It's whatever you want it to be.
- 你好像喝醉了  - 對
-You sound tipsy.  -I am.
我剛喝了兩小時的長島冰茶
I just spent the last two hours  drinking Long lsland lced Teas.
你的地址是什麼？
What's your address?
你的父母知道  你過這樣的生活嗎？
Do your parents know you live like this?
不知道，他們沒來看過我
No. They haven't visited.
有人照顧你嗎？
Are you cared for?
什麼意思？
How do you mean?
有男人照顧你嗎？
Do you have a man who cares for you?
- 上了年紀的男人  - 沒有
-An older man.  -No.
你跟上了年紀的男人交往過？
But you've been with older men before?
對
Yes.
在他們傷害你之後
Then you know they hurt you,
你知道他們傷害過你
and after they hurt you,
他們拋棄你
they discard you.
你不能傷害我
You can't hurt me.
脫掉你的高跟鞋
Take your heels off.